we need to modify the code we've been
given
so that the value of name is printed
within the string we see on line three
we want our expected output to say hello
elizabeth
let's run our code just as it is and see
what it outputs
so we can see our greeting and our
punctuation
and within that string we want to insert
the value of name
string interpolation allows us to put an
expression within a string
and ruby will call 2s on that value
the syntax for string interpolation is
the pound sign or octothorpe and curly
braces
so within these curly braces we can
place the local variable name
and ruby will insert the value
referenced by this local variable
the string elizabeth into our string
let's run our code
and we can see that we've gotten the
expected output
one important thing to note is that we
can only use this
string interpolation syntax within
double quotes
i'm going to replace our double quotes
with single quotes
and now let's take a look at our output
so one of the advantages of using double
quotes around our strings
is that we can easily use string
interpolation to
insert the value of a variable or
expression
into our string